Viewers all over the world, we have been releasing you from the hands of the devil.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
The deliverance that happened today - you have been delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
We say every shame the evil spirit has caused you - be it your health -
be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Every shame the evil spirit has caused you in your health, blood, fluids -
we remove that affliction, in the name of Jesus!
That affliction - leave, in the name of Jesus!
Career failure - leave, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Be it in your marriage, business, finances - be free and be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever chain, whatever medium satan might have used to connect you to himself -
to connect your body, health, blood, kidneys, liver -
be disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever chain satan might have used to connect your body, blood, kidneys -
be disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
That is satan for you - he is the cause of our career failure, he is the cause of that affliction,
he is the cause of setback - be disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
He is the cause of failure, stagnation, rejection, isolation.
Whatever chain satan might have used to connect you to himself -
you satan - be disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Be disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
I can see chains breaking!
I can see chains falling!
Fall, in the name of Jesus!
Say to yourself, "Chains have fallen!"
I can't hear you.
[Chains have fallen!]
Chain of sickness - has fallen!
Chain of disease - has fallen!
Chain of affliction - has fallen!
Chain of career failure - has fallen!
Chain of failure - has fallen!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, those on the sickbed,
I release you from that bed of sickness!
Be released from that bed of sickness!
Be released from that bed of sickness, affliction, disease!
Be released!
Be released from that bed of nightmare!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see you being released!
I can see you being released, in Jesus' name!
Give thanks to God for giving you the faith to believe that you are healed!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Mel Flowers 11/04/2019